United University Professions (UUP); Records apap039
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Labor Relations-Negotiations, 1968-1999; VI; 25.73 cubic ft.
  - Negotiations by Contract Year, 1971-1974 Contract to 1999-2003 Contract; 1; 9.53 cubic ft.
    - 1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED], 1.6; 2.07 cubic ft.
      - State of New York-UUP Factfinding Open Issues, Closed Issues, State Issues for Presentation, and Issue Details [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.6 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - State Proposals [RESTRICTED], January 16, 1985 (Box VI.1.6 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - State Supplemental Demands [RESTRICTED], January 30, 1985 (Box VI.1.6 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Tentative Agreement with UUP commentary sent to UUP Members (ratified and proofed copies) [RESTRICTED], March 1986 (Box VI.1.6 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
      - Tim Reilly Collected materials-Notes and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box VI.1.6 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
      - Tim Reilly Meeting Notes and Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box VI.1.6 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Team and Negotiations Sessions [RESTRICTED], January 9-February 27, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Team and Negotiations Sessions [RESTRICTED], March 6-April 10, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Team and Negotiations Sessions [RESTRICTED], May 8-June 19, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Team and Negotiations Sessions [RESTRICTED], July 8-November 26, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - UUP Amendments and Additions to Demands [RESTRICTED], January 30, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - UUP Demands [RESTRICTED], January 16, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - UUP Demands (F. Day annotated copy) [RESTRICTED], January 16, 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - UUP Demands (annotated 1st draft?) [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - UUP Demands (first draft) [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - UUP Demands "Committee Notes for First Draft" [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - UUP Demands, draft [RESTRICTED], January 1985 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - UUP Demands, "First Draft for Tim, Nuala and Sam" [RESTRICTED], December 10-15, 1984 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - UUP Demands, "Second Draft" [RESTRICTED], December 17, 1984 (Box VI.1.7 (1.6-1985-1988 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
    - 1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED], 1.7; 1.37 cubic ft.
      Contracts, correspondence, shorthand notes and typed transcripts of negotiations sessions and negotiations committee meetings. Transcripts sometimes include attachments such as additional proposals exchanged between State and UUP or other materials distributed at the negotiations sessions. The final transcript available for this contract covers a "debriefing" meeting held between UUP's negotiations team and negotiations committee the day after UUP signed the memorandum of understanding with the State.
      - Act of State Legislature to provide salary adjustments for State University employees in Professional Services Negotiating Unit [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on Negotiations [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - Agreement between State of New York and UUP (booklet) [RESTRICTED], September 13, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15A)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], August 1987-July 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
      - Collected Materials-EAP [RESTRICTED], November 17, 1987 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
      - Economic Impact of SUNY on Local Communities, Collected Reports [RESTRICTED], 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18-19)
      - Letter to Members on Tentative Agreement [RESTRICTED], June 14, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - Member lists-Negotiations Committee and Subcommittees [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - Memorandum of Understanding-Working Draft [RESTRICTED], May 23, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
      - Memorandum of Understanding-Working Draft [RESTRICTED], June 1, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
      - Memorandum of Understanding-Working Draft [RESTRICTED], June 9-10, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State of New York and UUP (signed original) [RESTRICTED], June 21, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State of New York and UUP (unsigned) [RESTRICTED], June 21, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - Negotiations Updates, Nos. 1-2 [RESTRICTED], December 1987; February 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26A)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #1 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], October 9, 1987-March 3, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #2 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], March 17-April 13, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #3 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], April 13-May 4, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #4 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], May 12-May 22, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - Negotiations Survey-General Statistics [RESTRICTED], October 6, 1987 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - Negotiations Update [RESTRICTED], March 28, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31A)
      - News Reports-Newspapers and UUP Publications [RESTRICTED], May 1987-May 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - Reference Compendium of documents referred to in contract or otherwise applicable to employees in Negotiating Unit [RESTRICTED], December 13, 1989 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - State Proposals [RESTRICTED], January 21, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - State Supplemental Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34A)
      - Tentative Agreement between UUP and State of New York mailed to members [RESTRICTED], June 29, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Committee and Negotiations Sessions (with attachments) [RESTRICTED], November 13/14, 1987-March 17, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Committee and Negotiations Sessions (with attachments) [RESTRICTED], March 23-April 22, 1988 (Box VI.1.7 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
      - Easel pages created by UUP negotiations team during preparation for 1988 negotiations (?) [RESTRICTED], ca. November 1987 (Box VI.1.7A (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]))
      - Transcripts and Minutes-Negotiations Committee and Negotiations Sessions (with attachments) [RESTRICTED], April 28-June 22, 1988 (Box VI.1.8 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - UUP Proposals [RESTRICTED], January 21, 1988 (Box VI.1.8 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - UUP Supplemental Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 22, 1988 (Box VI.1.8 (1.7-1988-1991 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
    - 1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED], 1.8; 0.60 cubic ft.
      UUP and State contract proposals; correspondence among negotiations team and with State; transcripts of negotiations sessions; contract text and text provided to membership for consideration. This subseries is supplemented by the records of Thomas Corigliano, Chief Negotiator, included in Series 4 in this Subgroup.
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], ca. July 1992 (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], July 1988-March 1993 (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Committee Listings [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, transcripts, etc. [RESTRICTED], August 1990-December 1990 (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, transcripts, etc. [RESTRICTED], January 1991-March 1991 (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, transcripts, etc. (plus index August 1990-April 1991) [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, transcripts, etc. [RESTRICTED], May 1991-July 2, 1991 (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, transcripts, etc. (plus index May 1991-March 1992) [RESTRICTED], July 16, 1991-March 1992 (Box VI.1.8 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - Final Agreement between UUP and State of New York (booklet) [RESTRICTED], December 4, 1992 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between UUP and State [RESTRICTED], June-July 1991; June 1992 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #1 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], August 23, 1990-March 8, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #2 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], March 8, 1991-April 18, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #3 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], April 19, 1991-June 7, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Negotiations Session Notebook #4 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], June 11, 1991-ca. November 15, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #5 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], November 15, 1991-June 23, 1992 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Negotiations Sessions Transcripts-Index by Article [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Notes, Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - State Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 7, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - State Proposal and Supplements [RESTRICTED], Spring 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - State Supplemental Proposals [RESTRICTED], April 26, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Tentative Agreement and Commentary-Special Negotiations Bulletin [RESTRICTED], July 27, 1992 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - UUP Proposal [RESTRICTED], February 7, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - UUP Proposal (annotated copy) [RESTRICTED], February 7, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - UUP Proposal and additional materials provided to State [RESTRICTED], Spring 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
      - UUP Supplemental Proposals [RESTRICTED], April 26, 1991 (Box VI.1.9 (1.8-1991-1995 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
    - 1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED], 1.9; 1.0 cubic ft.
      Final contract text; contract proposals of State and UUP; negotiation team and negotiations sessions transcripts; handouts and other materials from meetings of UUP negotiations team; correspondence to negotiating team and to State; compiled results of survey sent to members regarding issues for negotiations; notes on visits to chapters regarding member concerns; and negotiations bulletins. This subseries is supplemented by the records of Thomas Matthews, Chief Negotiator, included in Series 4 in this Subgroup, which include materials on specific issues of concern as well as materials regarding the delays experienced in obtaining a contract.
      - Agreement between State of New York and UUP (booklet) [RESTRICTED], September 30, 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Chapter Visit Notes [RESTRICTED], October 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Clinical Practice Negotiations Sessions [RESTRICTED], March 20-21, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - E-mail correspondence [RESTRICTED], September 1994-April 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Ground Rules for Negotiations [RESTRICTED], February 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Letter Agreement-Joint Committee on Health Benefits Amendment to List of Prospective Procedure Review procedures [RESTRICTED], May-June 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Letters Sent and Received [RESTRICTED], July 1994-September 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
      - Memoranda to UUP Negotiations Committee and Team [RESTRICTED], June 1994-December 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
      - Memoranda to UUP Negotiations Committee and Team [RESTRICTED], January 1995-August 1995; April 1996; March 1997-June 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between UUP and State [RESTRICTED], July 16, 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
      - Negotiating Team Meeting Notes [RESTRICTED], September 1994-February 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
      - Negotiations Bulletins, Nos. 1-3 [RESTRICTED], September 1994-April 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #1 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995-March 10, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #2 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], March 15, 1995-March 16, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #3 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], March 26, 1995-December 1, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #4 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], December 7, 1995-January 10, 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #5 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], January 11, 1996-February 2, 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Four Special Colleges (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Fourteen Colleges (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Institutional Types (by type) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Medical Schools (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Technical Colleges (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-University Centers (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
      - Proposals and Responses status chart; text of proposals from Voice [RESTRICTED], June 18, 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
      - State Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 11, 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
      - Team and Committee Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 11-13, 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
      - Team and Committee Meeting (transcript and committee reports) [RESTRICTED], November 11-13, 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], December 15, 1994 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], January 8-9, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
      - Team Meetings (miscellaneous handouts) [RESTRICTED], December 1995-January 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], February 10-13, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], March 2-3, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], August 17, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], October 13, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 16, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 30, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], March 26, 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], September 19, 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], July 10, 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
      - Team Meetings (miscellaneous handouts) [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
      - Tentative Contract Agreement -- special negotiations bulletin mailed to members [RESTRICTED], August 18, 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
      - Transcripts - Negotiations Sessions and Negotiations Team [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995-March 21, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
      - Transcripts - Negotiations Sessions and Negotiations Team [RESTRICTED], March 23, 1995-December 14, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
      - Transcripts - Negotiations Sessions and Negotiations Team [RESTRICTED], January 1996-April 13, 1996 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
      - UUP Contract Proposal "Actual Language" [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
      - UUP Counterproposal [RESTRICTED], March 28, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
      - UUP Crisis Bulletin (vols. 2-11) and News Release [RESTRICTED], February 1, 1995-April 7, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
      - UUP Negotiations Committee and Team Lists [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
      - UUP Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
      - UUP Proposals - drafts, summaries, talking points [RESTRICTED], February-March 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
      - UUP Supplemental Contract Proposals [RESTRICTED], March 15, 1995 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
      - Voice issues re: tentative contract and contract ratification [RESTRICTED], September-October 1997 (Box VI.1.10 (1.9-1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
    - 1999-2003 Contract [RESTRICTED], 1.10; 0.17 cubic ft.
      Text of final contract and addendum to contract; negotiations bulletin sent to members with text of, and commentary on, contract; tabulated results of survey of members used in preparation for negotiations.
      - 1998 Negotiations Survey Data [RESTRICTED], November 1998 (Box VI.1.11 (1.10-1999-2003 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Addendum to Agreement between the of New York and UUP [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.11 (1.10-1999-2003 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Agreement between State of New York and UUP (booklet) [RESTRICTED], July 2, 1999 (Box VI.1.11 (1.10-1999-2003 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - Special Negotiations Bulletin--text of tentative agreement with commentary [RESTRICTED], August 20, 1999 (Box VI.1.11 (1.10-1999-2003 Contract [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Non-Contract Specific Materials, 1971-1989; 2; 1.0 cubic ft.
    - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1972-1989; 2.1; 0.25 cubic ft.
      Correspondence between UUP and the Governor's Office of Employee Relations, reports on collective bargaining in higher education, memoranda of understanding between UUP and the State on evaluation and promotion of professionals, negotiation surveys and other correspondence and materials not obviously related to a specific contract or that overlap contract years.
      - Collected Materials-"Contract Issues" (including tenure, retrenchment, less than full year appointments, and tuition assistance) [RESTRICTED], 1974-1981 (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
      - Contract Ratification Procedures [RESTRICTED], ca. 1979? (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
      - Correspondence with GOER [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
      - "Higher Education Collective Bargaining: Other than Faculty Personnel", Volume 1, National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, Baruch College, CUNY [RESTRICTED], December 1974 (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State of New York and UUP regarding health insurance coverage [RESTRICTED], November 17, 1982 (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
      - Memorandum of Understanding Relating to Evaluation and Promotion Systems for Professional Employees in the State University of New York (booklet) [RESTRICTED], April 1977 (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State University of New York and UUP Relating to Systems of Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees (reprint) [RESTRICTED], November 1983 (Box VI.2.1 (2.1-Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)